<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <record id="contract_agreement_print" model="ir.actions.report">
        <field name="name">Contract Agreement</field>
        <field name="model">hr.contract</field>
        <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
        <field name="report_name">stadia.contract_agreement_template</field>
        <field name="report_file">contract_agreement</field>
        <field name="print_report_name">'Contract agreement for Employment - %s' % (object.id)</field>
        <field name="paperformat_id" ref="paperformat_euro_lowmargin"/>
        <!-- model_[model name] -->
        <field name="binding_model_id" ref="model_hr_contract"/>
        <field name="binding_type">report</field>
    </record>

    <template id="contract_agreement_template">
        <t t-call="web.basic_layout">
            <style>
                .header-1 {
                    justify-content: space-between;
                    border: 0px solid red;
                    padding: 2px 5px;
                    display: flex;
                    flex-direction: row;
                }
                .vl {
                    border-left: 6px solid rgb(224, 13, 6);
                    height: 75px;
                    position: absolute;
                    left: 40%;
                    top: 0;
                }
                .div-agree {
                    margin-left: 200px;
                }
                ol.orderlist {
                    list-style-type: square;
                }
                ol.list-alpa {
                    list-style-type: upper-alpha;
                }
                .badge_img {
                    margin-left: 100px;
                    width: 50px;
                    height: 50px;
                    left: 70%;
                }
                .witness {
                    margin-left: 60px;
                }
                .underline-text {
                    text-decoration: underline;
                    text-decoration-thickness: 15px;
                }
                .jst-line {
                    border: 0;
                    border-bottom: 2px solid #000;
                    margin-bottom: 5px;
                }
            </style>
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="data">
            <div class="header-1">
                <div>
                    <h7>EMPLOYEMENT AREEMENT</h7>
                </div>
                <div class="vl"></div>
                <div>
                    <img src="/stadia/static/stadia_logo.jpg" class="badge_img" />
                </div>
                <div class="div-right">
                    STADIA ENGINEERING AND WORKS CONSULTANT PLC.
                </div>
            </div>
            <hr />
            <hr/>
            <div class="div-agree">
                <u>
                    <h2>EMPLOYEMENT AGREEMENT</h2>
                </u>
            </div>
            <div>
                <p>
                    1. This permanent employment is made and entered into this <b><t t-esc="data['date_start']" /></b> by and between, STADIA
                    Engineering
                    Works Consultant Plc, having its registered office at 9th floor, NB Building, near Wuha Limat, Addis Ababa,
                    Ethiopia,
                    hereinafter referred to as the “Employer”, and
                    <t t-esc="data['employee_id']['title']" />
                    <input type="text" class="jst-line" t-att-value="data['employee_id']['name']"/>
                    , address: Sub city <input type="text" class="jst-line" t-att-value="data['employee_id']['sub_city_id']['name']"/> Wereda <input type="text" class="jst-line" t-att-value="data['employee_id']['woreda']"/>,
                    House
                    No. <input type="text" class="jst-line" t-att-value="data['employee_id']['house_number']"/> Phone number +251 <input type="text" class="jst-line" t-att-value="data['employee_id']['mobile_phone']"/> Tin no <t t-esc="data['employee_id']['tin_no']" /> Bank account no <input type="text" class="jst-line" t-att-value="data['employee_id']['bank_account_id']"/>  hereinafter
                    referred
                    to as “Employee”.<br />
        
                    2. Whereas the Employer desires to assign the Employee as a <b>Highway Engineer</b> with a written permanent
                    employment
                    contract to undertake the duties and responsibilities of the Highway Engineer included in the Service
                    Contract
                    document. <br />
                    3. Now, therefore, the Employer and the Employee, for the consideration herein specified, agree as follows.
                    <br />
                    3.1 TERMS
                <ul>
                    <li>The Employer hereby employs, and the Employee hereby accepts
                        employment as Highway Engineer for the project starting from <b><t t-esc="data['date_start']" /></b></li>
        
                </ul><br />
                3.2 TYPICAL ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITY <br />
                <ul>
                    <li>Planning, co-ordination and day-to-day control of all project activities</li><br />
                    <li>Continuous liaison with the Contractor and Employer's Representative including preparation and
                        issue of progress reports and required deliverables as per our schedule</li><br />
                    <li>Establishment and control of project related quality assurance routines</li><br />
                    <li>Monitoring of progress of work compared with planned progress</li><br />
                    <li>Will carry out investigation of road alignment geometry in order to assure a safe, economical and
                        comfortable alignment taking into account the terrain
                        conditions, traffic nature anticipated, the proposed design standard and environmental conditions.</li>
                    <br />
                    <br />
                    <li>Will conduct a physical assessment of the selected route corridor along the other proposed route.</li>
                    <br />
                    <li>Instruct and supervise the surveying activities for the final design work of the road project.</li><br />
                    <li>Carryout preliminary geometric design of the proposed alignments so as to get prior approval of the
                        preliminary design from the Contractor and Employer's Representative before proceeding
                        to the detailed design work using a modern and comprehensive CADD package and MX-Road road design
                        software</li><br />
                    <li>Will show horizontal and vertical curves control criteria to justify that the design is as per
                        the requirements of the design standard</li><br />
                    <li>Indicate the locations of proposed structures (culverts and bridges) by investigating their
                        geometrical suitability of the preliminary geometric design in that locality</li><br />
                    <li>Will thoroughly examine Right of Way requirements</li><br />
                    <li>Will thoroughly examine consumption of productive land and other natural resources</li><br />
                    <li>Closely follow up and monitor the route corridor selection, check procedure of analysis.</li><br />
                    <li>will define general and specific Road design parameters such as:</li><br />
                    <ol class="orderlist">
                        <li>Design speeds to be adopted for the various road sections;</li> <br />
                        <li>Typical cross-sections for the various road sections, together
                            with the upgrade/widening proposals (cross-section development);</li><br />
                        <li>The minimum horizontal and vertical alignment criteria for various design speeds;</li><br />
                        <li>Super elevation criteria for the different design speeds;</li><br />
                        <li>Geometric design parameters regarding lane widths, type of pavements, road signs and speed control;
                        </li><br />
                    </ol>
                </ul>
                3.3 PROBATION<br />
                <ul>
                    <li>The employee shall go probation of 60 Working days from the first day of employment to determine his/her
                        suitability for the post.
                        If during this period the Employer fined the Employee unfit for the job he can terminate the contract
                        of employment without being obliged to give prior notice, pay severance pay of compensation.</li>
                </ul>
                3.4 PLACE OF WORK<br />
                <ul>
                    <li>The employee shall be assigned to work at Head Office.However; the company may transfer the employees to
                        other projects.</li>
                </ul>
                3.5 CONTRACT AMOUNT<br />
                <ul>
                    <li>The Employer shall pay the Employee a gross monthly contract amount of ETB <b><t t-esc="data['wage']" /></b> per day. </li>
                    <li>This indicated monthly contract amount shall be paid to the Employee on a monthly basis. </li>
                </ul>
                3.6 WORKING HOURS<br />
                <ul>
                    <li>The Employee’s normal working hours shall be 48 hours on a week.</li>
                    <li>The employer from time to time depending on the employer’s operational needs shall determine the time of
                        reporting to and departure from work.</li>
                </ul>
                3.7 OVER TIME <br />
                <ul>
                    <li>The Employer may in accordance with the labor proclamation 1156/2011 require the
                        Employee to work overtime. The payment of such work shall be computed as per the above-mentioned
                        proclamation.</li>
                    <li>The Employee shall be entitled to 16 working days of Annual leave for the first year of service,
                        plus one working day for every additional Two years of service.</li>
                </ul>
                3.9 SICK LEAVE <br />
                <ul>
                    <li>When the employee is unable to carry out his/her duties owing to sickness other than resulting from
                        employment injury he shall be entitled to a sick leave up to six months’ period starting from the first
                        day of his/her sickness.</li>
                    <li>The sick leave mentioned here in above shall be given to the employee in the following manner.</li>
                    <ol class="list-alpa">
                        <li>The first one-month with 100% of his/her wage.</li>
                        <li>The next two months with 50% of his/her wage.</li>
                        <li>The next three months without pay.</li>
                    </ol>
                </ul>
                3.10 TERMINATION OF EMPLOYMENT CONTRACT<br />
                Termination of Employment Contract may be made by: <br />
                <ul>
                    <li>Completion of the project;</li>
                    <li>Mutual agreement of the parties; </li>
                    <li>Retirement of the Employee; </li>
                    <li>Termination by the Employer; </li>
                    <li>In such cases, both parties shall give a minimum of 30 days’ notice to terminate this contract. </li>
                </ul>
                4 In witness, thereof, we hereby sign this contract this -- day of <b><t t-esc="data['date_start']" />.</b> <br />
        
                Employer________________________ Employee ___________________________ <br />
                <div class="witness">
                    <br />
                    <br />
                    Witness<br />
        
                    1. ________________________<br />
        
        
                    2. ________________________<br />
        
        
                    3. ________________________<br />
                </div>
        
                </p>
            </div>
        </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>